What is it ?
Can you hear it ?
What ?
- It 's a squonk . - A squonk ?
And what 's that ?
The squonk ?
You surprise me .
A girl of your intelligence doesn 't know what a squonk is ?
It 's an animal covered in moles
that can camouflage itself perfectly .
I think it 's exclusively female , but it 's easy to find
because it 's very vain and it never stops whining .
And when it 's captured ... it dissolves into tears .
You act like a thief where love 's concerned .
You take it and run .
Other characteristics of the squonk are sulkiness , diffidence
and possessiveness .
Very inconvenient qualities for a personal secretary .
Well , more than that ...
a partner in an affair as important as this .
- Where are you going ? - To the bay .
We 're on the home stretch , I 've got to close the deal .
The police suspended investigations into the Countess ' death ,
there was no evidence .
A case of suicide .
Everything 's fine .
I just need a signature .
Bye !
- Franco ! - Yes ?
- Take me with you . - Better not right now .
Maybe later .
But call me first .
Bye , squonk !
Bye . Be careful !
Give them to me !
You 'll have a heart attack chasing after that bug !
How do you know it 's the same one ?
Because it 's the only insect that 's escaped you .
Not the only , but he
is very intelligent and remembers last autumn
when I put a ring round one of his horns and let him go .
- Why ? - To study his habits .
Sure ... to see if he 's horny !
Men should leave others to enjoy their freedom .
Even that poor octopus was free once , Simone .
I study beetles because I love them .
Yes , you pin them to boards
or preserve them in display cases .
At least I eat my octopus .
I don 't kill as a hobby like you !
My God , Simon , you make me feel like a murderer !
I didn 't say that , Mr Fossati .
When one kills contrary to the laws of nature , one becomes a monster .
But man isn 't an insect , dear Simon .
We have thousands of years of civilization behind us .
I don 't know about that .
I wasn 't there .
You 've changed
ever since Federica was killed .
Suicide ... Mr Fosatti .
Suicide .
The police said it was suicide .
Of course ...
Sorry ... a slip of the tongue !
Don 't worry , Your Honour .
By tonight I 'll have all the documents signed by the heir .
Of course .
No , everything 's in order .
We 'll wait a while before starting work , out of respect .
The poor Countess ... well , she came to a rather nasty end .
Of course , I don 't think I 'm underestimating your problems .
But it 's an important enough deal to justify a bit of a risk .
Leave it to me , Your Honour .
Everything will go smoothly . Just take care of the permits .
Okay , Your Honour . Certainly .
I 'll drop by and see you .
My respects , Your Honour .
Ready , sir .
- Here . Goodbye . - Thanks .
Look how beautiful it is !
Look , it 's lovely ! It 's like a paradise on earth .
Well , we mustn 't fall from grace here then !
Why not ? That 's what we came for !
Go , Roberto !
- Hands off ! - I haven 't even started yet .
Yes , you have !
- Fetrol , gentlemen ? - Petrol !
You 've been here a year and you can 't say it yet !
You Italians only teach us the dirty words !
Come on , Roberto !
Who cares , we didn 't come here to teach them Italian .
- Don 't you like me anymore ? - I 'll show you how much !
Look how lonely it is here !
Come on , Robert .
Come on ...
We 've found a night club , come on ! There 's even a dance floor !
Let 's go ! At least we can dance !
Louise , give me the tape recorder .
Here it is !
Sylvie , put on some music . It 's like a mausoleum in here !
No point trying to set the scene for some Latin seduction !
This place is more Sibelius than Puccini !
Hold the culture !
Come on , climb up ! You too !
Great , there 's a platform too ! Come on , Robert , let 's do the shake !
You and me will do the tango .
The Aleph
the one ... the all ...
the void ...
The lines of air , water , fire and earth
are complete .
Paolo !
You could at least answer when I call !
Don 't yell , you 'll upset the little fellows .
You and your hateful bugs !
It 's be absurd to think you 're capable of love .
Me ?
I love many things , but you 'd never understand .
We don 't understand anything , right , Ferdinando ?
Clouds of blood are gathering over the bay .
Really ? Just think , Ferdinando ! Now what ?
The Aleph came out at the end of the line of fire .
The Zaren was suspended between the lines of water and air .
The sickle of death is about to strike !
Oh really , your cards sometimes !
Last week the Aleph came out first
and gusts of joy were going to blow over The Bay .
Instead someone hanged poor Federica !
You 're more insensitive than your beetles !
Can 't you feel the chill of death 's icy breath ?
All I hear is Ventura holding the usual orgy in his cottage !
You hate Ventura for the same reason you hated Federica 's husband ,
because he enjoys life and you don 't !
The formalin , be careful !
I hate him because he wants to turn The Bay into a sea of cement .
But I won 't let him ! Even if I have to ...
- Not dancing , Robert ? - I 'm no good at it .
Come on !
I 'll take you to a private room .
Stop it ! You 're tickling me !
I only do it in bed . And it must be comfortable !
Bourgeois !
I 'm coming !
You big , sexy doll !
Come and see the swimming pool !
God , what a stink !
Here I go !
Careful , you 'll trip !
I 'll dive in !
I 'm coming , Roberto !
Are you mad ? Want to get typhus ? There might be a corpse in there .
You always say terrible things !
Maybe I found the bed .
- I 'm going to swim in the sea . - You 'll get pneumonia .
- You want to die here ? - Let 's go . Come on !
- Let 's go and find this bed . - But let 's bring Roberto too .
Why him ?
Don 't leave me with this maniac !
Come on , boys !
What do you want ? Go for a swim !
- In this cold ? - Yes , this cold !
She 's used to it . In her country they eat whale blubber .
- It 's like a museum . - Maybe there 's a watchman !
If you 're scared , beat it .
Go on , push !
I knew it 'd be locked .
Let 's not be stupid ! This is private property .
- And the bed ? - Luca will take care of that !
Don 't worry . A locked door won 't stop me !
Come on , Luca ! Show us what you 're made of !
Don 't you like girls ?
What is this , a threesome ?
- Actually , I ... - You did it , you 're fantastic !
Come on , Roberto , you 're invited too .
Where are you going ? Look , yours is in the water .
The bed !
Sylvie , go check out the bed .
I 'll be right with you .
The party 's over for you .
You dumped the other one to bother us ? Are you a voyeur ?
Here , be a native , but do it outside !
Where 's Roberto ?
Just when I 've found the bed !
What do you care about Roberto ? I 'm here , aren 't I ?
Leave me alone !
Rapist !
Don 't be so rough ! Where are you taking me ?
Roberto , is that you ?
Roberto , answer me !
Don 't fool around !
I found a body !
Hell 's bells !
He always pretends he can 't hear !
Well , Alberto ? Are you coming ?
The kids .
It took me half an hour to get them to go to sleep .
- Why leave the light on ? - You know they don 't like the dark .
If you 'd listened to me , they 'd be at their aunt 's now ,
but your sentimentalism ...
At that harridan 's ?
Kids should be with their parents .
Don 't start ! Think about what to ask the Fossatis .
Me ? I thought I didn 't know how to think !
It 's the truth , or we wouldn 't be reduced to this !
Good evening !
Are you Mr Fossati ?
I 'm Donati 's daughter . I 'd like some information about my father .
Is it convenient ?
Excuse me , may we come in ?
I 'd like to talk to your wife too .
Of course , Filippo Donati 's death
threw a very strange light on dear Federica 's death .
Suicide , said the police .
But ...
Suicide ! Her !
I knew her well .
She clung to life , and how !
And she clung to her property even more !
As I understand it , what you actually want to say is that
Federica wouldn 't have committed suicide but ...
Excuse me if I 'm frank , ma 'am , but
your father wasn 't suited to this place .
Right , Ferdinando ? Drink ! Another drop , and then to bed !
And tomorrow morning a nice flight in the woods !
Excuse me , but ,
you father was ... a bit ... you understand ?
Women ... gambling ...
escapades of every kind ...
The idea to turn The Bay into a luxury resort
was always doomed to failure
because , as you can see , dear lady ,
this place is full of insects
I imagine that 's why the two of you came to live here then .
My husband believes that even insects have a soul .
On the other hand , if Filippo Donati has a soul ,
insects also do .
Maybe Renata meant that you settled here
for the natural life .
Natural or unnatural , one could even kill one 's wife
if it meant would one could enjoy life more fully .
I came to find out about my father 's disappearance ,
not to hear judgement passed on him .
I don 't understand what you 're getting at .
Nothing .
Nothing , my dear lady .
I just hope you don 't intend to reopen the night club ,
the gas station and all the other devilries installed by your father
that have almost destroyed the fauna here .
If you manage to inherit The Bay .
- Remember all that , Ferdinando ? - Ferdinando doesn 't remember .
- Ferdinando doesn 't remember ... - No !
Inheriting isn 't so easy .
Maybe Federica 's will
leaves everything to her biological son .
Biological son ?
Yes ! Federica did have her brighter moments .
Didn 't you know Simone is the fruit of her secret love affair ?
No , actually . Who is this Simone ?
He lives in a cabin by The Bay .
He 's part watchman , part woodsman , part petty thief .
- Anna ! - What ?
He 's a good chap , but lately he 's had some strange ideas .
Federica kept him in college until he was 16 .
Then she had him build that cabin and kept him there like an animal .
A constant reminder of her weak flesh .
Maybe he knows something about my father .
I doubt it , he always avoided him .
He didn 't approve of your father 's marriage to Federica .
But we should ask him if he knows anything .
Maybe Franco Ventura might know something .
He owns the cottage nearby . He knows your father very well .
It 's better not to take the car .
See that path ?
It 'll take you straight there .
What did you do to your hand ?
I cut myself with the penknife .
Your father 's disappearance wasn 't enough , now there 's a son too !
We 're even worse off than before !
If you 'd stop whining and use your brain , you 'd find a solution .
- There 's no way out . - There , you 've already given up .
There 's only one thing between us and that inheritance .
- What ? - Nothing !
Okay , Simone , tomorrow ...
Go and see who they are !
Are you Simone ?
No , everything 's fine .
Tomorrow we 'll celebrate together .
As soon as we get the go ahead , I 'll take a long holiday .
No , you 've got to keep things moving .
I can 't right now .
Nothing , just a little complication .
No , nothing serious .
Come on , don 't start !
I said no !
Okay , get all the details and I 'll take care of it .
Okay ...
Bye , squonk !
You don 't remember when you last saw Filippo Donati ?
You must have had some dealings with him .
You 've lived here for years , this isn 't New York !
He was the owner of The Bay .
But you knew him , right ?
You 're a man of few words !
It 's horrible ! It 's my father !
I feel sick !
I found him in the sea .
Take her to Ventura 's cottage , it 's over there .
Mr Ventura !
Come on , calm down .
Looks like there 's no one here . How are you ? Feeling better ?
Get the car , hurry !
I heard your wife scream .
We found Donati 's body .
- Where ? - In Simone 's boat .
- Have you seen my wife ? - Down there , on the path .
That busybody ! Anna !
Alberto ! Come here , quick !
- Did you see ? - Yes , I did it .
- You did it ? - Why that face ?
This isn 't the right moment to get all sensitive !
Stop that idiot before he calls the police and ruins everything .
- But how ? - Go on , move it !
Go on , go !
Police ...
332 ...
Three ... three ... two .
Hello ? Police ?
Three ... three ... two ...
Give me a full tank .
- Is there a ' phone here ? - Yes , it 's inside .
- Should I check the oil ? - Yes , thanks .
Stop yelling , are you crazy ?
I killed him .
Those two could have saved themselves
if they 'd minded their own business .
Now there are no more witnesses .
You mean that you ...
- The wife too ? - Don 't be such an old woman !
In certain situations you have to act decisively .
Old woman ? I just killed a man !
Listen , let 's get out of here .
Things will turn nasty .
If you 're such a coward as to dump everything on my shoulders , do it .
I won 't give up The Bay when it 's ours for the taking .
But how ?
Haven 't you understood ?
Simone ! We just have to get rid of Simone .
Who 's that ?
What if she saw us ?
We 'll do what we have to .
Laura !
- My God ! What happened ? - Get Simone , quick .
- But you 're wounded ! - Simone !
Bring Simone here , quick !
Don 't waste time .
Ventura 's wounded , quick ! He needs help !
- Why did you close it ? - You finally came back to The Bay .
What do you mean ?
You convinced that bastard , Donati , to kill my mother .
Your mother ?
Me ?
Don 't play the innocent , you whore !
Whore !
You drove him to murder !
You wanted him to marry you at all costs !
You wanted to become Mistress of The Bay !
But now I 'll you like I killed him !
I had nothing to do with it !
I was dragged into this against my will .
I didn 't want to , let me explain . I was forced !
It was Ventura , that 's the truth .
It was all Ventura 's idea .
He wanted to buy The Bay .
It seems immoral to let The Bay disappear under the vegetation
when it could ... - Disappear under cement ?
I already suffered enough over The Bay .
I prefer the chaos of vegetation over what you 'd like to bring here .
But it 's not for love of property that I keep it .
If my house wasn 't here , I 'd have sold The Bay long ago .
I assure you that I would retain it 's natural beauty .
I 'd only build villas ... very exclusive , modern .
Your reasons are not sufficient to convert me to modernism .
I already made the mistake of entrusting The Bay
to someone with a penchant for modernism .
Excuse me , but your husband ...
I don 't want to hear another word about that man !
We could review the price if that 's the problem .
A gentleman would not insist so much , Mr Ventura .
Excuse me , it 's time for my nap .
- Young lady ... - Countess ...
Even the most stubborn can be persuaded to think again .
" January 8th . I am now sure that Filippo feels estranged from me .
I agreed to his project for developing The Bay
in the hope of saving our marriage .
Instead it 's floundering . "
Stop it , I don 't care about the Countess ' love life .
Here ! It was all over between them on February 13th .
Listen .
" February 13th . It 's over .
I 'm tired , my life has no purpose . "
Poor thing ! She must have been devastated !
Read that page again .
" It 's over . I 'm tired , my life has no purpose . "
What is it ?
February 13th ...
Tell me , didn 't Donati once take a liking to you ?
Don 't be ridiculous .
I met him when you took me to that night club at The Bay .
It 's time to let him start courting you again .
In fact , you 're the one who 'll court him .
What do you intend to do ?
It 's simple .
Look .
What does it mean ?
The Countess is tired of life and commits suicide .
Suicide ?
Yes .
On February 13th , just like it says here .
On the night of the 13th , Donati will kill the Countess .
The next day the body will be found with a suicide note beside it .
Donati inherits the bay and sells it to me .
Clear ?
If Donati falls in love with you , things could be a lot easier .
He pushed me into seeing Donati .
Then Ventura intervened himself .
He was the one who carried out the plan .
That bastard !
And you 're worse than him !
I loved that poor cripple !
You killed her for this shitty bay !
And me ... I was stupid enough
to let you involve me in your dirty deal .
I 'll kill you !
Bastards !
I 'll kill all of you !
No ! I said no !
You can 't keep teasing me like this !
I don 't want to be the other woman .
Get rid of Federica .
- Then we 'll see . - I thought about it , but
it 's not that easy .
But it seems to be the only way .
So , will you do it ?
I had to do it , they found Donati 's body .
You 've got yourself into some serious trouble .
Put them in the bathroom for now , then we 'll dump them in the sea .
You 'd better get out of here , go abroad !
Where will I get the money ?
That can be arranged .
If you sign over The Bay to me , you could get a loan .
But get me a copy of that will so it 's all above board .
Okay .
Here , sign .
Good . Tomorrow morning you 'll get your money ,
air ticket and passport .
Thank you .
There are two more things ...
come on .
They 're here , I 've found them .
What 's happening ?
Renata , where are you ?
Yes ?
I didn 't think you had it in you .
It 's the least I could do for my family .
We 'd better clear out of here .
We 'll come back as owners , when The Bay is legally handed over .
It was lucky we found my father 's body .
Now no one can accuse him of being a murderer .
All 's well that ends well !
Mummy ! Daddy !
They 're good at playing dead , aren 't they ?
Let 's go to the bay !